<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kalima</string>
    <string name="title_activity_kalima_page1">kalima_page1</string>


    <string name="kalimapart1">

            "لآ اِلَهَ اِلّا اللّهُ مُحَمَّدٌ رَسُوُلالل\n"


    </string>
    <string name="kalimapart2">

 "There is none worthy of worship except Allah and Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="kalimapart3">

        "Laaa Ilaaha Illa-llaahu Muhammadur- Rasoolu-llaah\n"

    </string>

    <string name="kalimapart4">
        "/اَشْهَدُ اَنْ لَّآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللهُ وَحْدَہٗ لَاشَرِيْكَ لَہٗ وَاَشْهَدُ اَنَّ مُحَمَّدًا عَبْدُهٗ وَرَسُولُہٗ‎"
    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart5">
       "Bear witness that there is none worthy of worship except Allah,"
        "the One alone, without partner, and I bear witness that Muhammad is His servant and Messenger"
    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart6">
        "Ash-hadu Al-laaa Ilaaha Illa-llaahu Wahdahoo Laa Shareeka Lahoo"
        "Wa-Ash-hadu Anna Muhammadan ‘Abduhoo Wa Rasooluhu."


    </string>
    <string name="kalimapart7">
        "سُبْحَان اللهِ وَالْحَمْدُلِلّهِ وَلا إِلهَ إِلّااللّهُ وَاللّهُ أكْبَرُ وَلا حَوْلَ وَلاَ قُوَّةَ إِلَّا بِاللّهِ الْعَلِيِّ الْعَظِيْم‎"

    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart8">
        "Glory be to Allah and all praise be to Allah, there is none worthy of worship except Allah, and Allah is the Greatest.\n"
        "There is no might or power except from Allah, the Exalted, the Great One.\n"

    </string>

    <string name="kalimapart9">
        "Subhaana-llaahi Walhamdu Lillaahi Walaaa Ilaaha Illa-llaahu Wallaahu Akbar.\n"
        "Walaa Hawla Walaa Quwwata Illaa Billaahi-l ‘Aliyyil ‘Azeem\n"
    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart10">
        "لَآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللهُ وَحْدَهٗ لَا شَرِيْكَ لَهٗ لَهُ الْمُلْكُ وَ لَهُ"
        "الْحَمْدُ يُحْىٖ وَ يُمِيْتُ وَ هُوَحَیٌّ لَّا يَمُوْتُ اَبَدًا اَبَدًاؕ ذُو"
        "الْجَلَالِ وَالْاِكْرَامِؕ بِيَدِهِ الْخَيْرُؕ وَهُوَ عَلٰى كُلِّ شیْ ٍٔ قَدِیْر"ٌؕ"

    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart11">
        "There is none worthy of worship except Allah. He is alone and has no partner.\n"
        To Him belongs the Kingdom and for Him is all praise. He gives life and causes death.\n"
        In His hand is all good and He has power over everything.\n"

    </string>

    <string name="Kalimapart12">
        "Laaa Ilaaha Illa-llaahu Wahdahoo Laa Shareeka-lahoo Lahu Mulku Walahu\n"
        Hamdu Yuhyee Wayumeetu Wahuwa Hayyu Laa Yamootu Abadan Abada.\n"
        Dhu Jalaali Wal Ikraam. Biyadihil Khair. Wahuwa Alaa Kulli Shai-’in Qadeer.\n"

    </string>
    <string name="Kalimapart13">

"اَللّٰهُمَّ اِنِّیْٓ اَعُوْذُ بِكَ مِنْ اَنْ اُشْرِكَ بِكَ شَيْئًا وَّاَنَآ اَعْلَمُ بِهٖ وَ اَسْتَغْفِرُكَ لِمَا لَآ"
        "اَعْلَمُ بِهٖ تُبْتُ عَنْهُ وَ تَبَرَّأْتُ مِنَ الْكُفْرِ وَ الشِّرْكِ وَ الْكِذْبِ وَ الْغِيْبَةِ وَ الْبِدْعَةِ وَ النَّمِيْمَةِ وَ الْفَوَاحِشِ و"َ
        "الْبُهْتَانِ وَ الْمَعَاصِىْ كُلِِّهَا وَ اَسْلَمْتُ وَ اَقُوْلُ لَآ اِلٰهَ اِلَّا اللهُ مُحَمَّدٌ رَّسُوْلُ الله"ِؕ

    </string>
    <string name="Kalimapart14">
        "O Allah! I seek refuge in You from that I should ascribe any partner with You knowingly.\n"
        "I seek Your forgiveness for the sin of which I have no knowledge.\n"
        "lying and backbiting, innovation and slander,\n"
        "lewdness and abomination and all other acts of disobedience,\n"
        "I submit to Your will.I believe and I declare that there is none worthy of\n"
        "worship except Allah and Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Kalimapart15">
        "Allaa-humma Inneee A’udhu-bika Min An Ushrika Bika Shay-awn Wa-ana A’lamu Bihee Wa-\n"
        "astaghfiruka Limaa Laaa A’lamu Bihee Tubtu ‘Anhu Wata-barraatu Mina-l Kufri Wash-shirki Wal-kidhbi\n"
        "Wal-gheebati Wal-bid’ati Wan-nameemati Wal-fawahishi Wal-buhtaani Wal-m’aasi Kulli-haa\n"
        "Wa-Aslamtu Wa-aqoolu Laaa Ilaaha Illa-llaahu Muhammadu-r Rasoolu-llah\n"
    </string>


</resources>
